Pietro Belluschi Papers
Pietro Belluschi Papers
- Correspondence-subject files, 1991 accession
  - Juries etc.
    - Boston juries, parcel 8, 3 folders (Box 531)
Willamette University, Music Building, Salem, OR 695
Willamette University, [unspecified], Salem, OR [no number]
Willamette University, Science Building 624
Williams, C. K. 99
Wilson house 1171
Wilson Lumber Co. office, Warm Springs, OR 1226
Wilson, Charles house, Deshutes River, OR 1016
Wilson, Robert house, Deshutes River, OR 1017
Winfree, A. B. house [no number]
Witlock, John P. 248
Wolverton, C. E. house 136
Woodward, Clarke & Co. 141
Woodward, Clarke & Co., Woodlark Building 145
Worcester Building 15
Worcester Center, Worcester, MA3016 [no number]
Work, A. M. house, Seaside, OR 1173
Worker's hotel [no number]
World Trade Center, Baltimore, MD [no number]
Wren Tea House [no number]
Wright house 723
Yakima Valley Bank [no number]
Yeon Building 498
Yeon, J. B. house alterations [no number]
YMCA, Portland, OR 417
YWCA, Pittsburgh, PA [no number]
YWCA, Salem, OR 1001
Zell Bros. 955
Zimmerman's 12 Mile Store, Gresham, OR 871
Zion Lutheran Church, Portland, OR 1090
Zoods Port Angeles Store alterations, Port Angeles, WA 1216